Guide to the International Association for Cultural Freedom Records 1941-1978
University of Chicago Library
- Series VII: Preuves Papers
  - Subseries 20: Manuscripts
    - Manuscripts, Gajcy-Gombrowicz, 1959-1967, Gajcy, Tadeusz Galczynski, Konstanty I. Galka de Dobczyn, Andrej Gallego, Julian Georgel, Pierre Gilles, Daniel Goeky, A. Goldenberg Gombrowicz, Witold, "Sur Bruno Schulz" Gombrowicz, "Journal Intime" Gombrowicz, "Le Mariage" (Box 649, Folder 2)
    - Manuscripts, Gombrich-Grand, 1959-1966, Gombrich, E. H., "Je pense avoir tiré de la..." Gombrich, E. H., "L'esthétique de Freud" Gomulicki, Wiktor Goriely, Georges Gossec, "Paradoxe sur les Prix" Gossec, "Une Année Mahler" Gossec, "Du Quevedo Musica" Gossec, "Pressages et Façons" Gossec, "D'un Bluff trop commode" Gossec, "Orfeo bis" Grabowiecki, Sebastion "Grand Prix de la Nouvelle" (Correspondence, Judges' votes, Winning manuscripts, etc.) (Box 649, Folder 3)
    - Manuscripts, Grass-Graves, 1964, Grass, Gunter, "Les etudiants oues - allemands du S.D.S. ont..." Grass, "Sous le train de Bois" Grass, "Admettons - le: avec sa barbiche..." Grass, "Lettre Ouverte Aux Membres de l'Association des Ecrivains Allemands" Graves, Robert, "Deyá, mi pueblo hace 32 años" Graves, "Juana Inés de la Cruz" (Box 649, Folder 4)
    - Manuscripts, Greiner-Havel, 1963-1968, Greiner, Mechtilt Meijer Gresset, Michel Grina, R. Grochowiak, Stanislaw Guellouz, Jelila Guibert, Armand, "Un Cadavre Qui Bouge Encore" Guibert, "Lorca de Soleil et d'Ombre" Guibert, "Negritude ou Africanité?" Guibert, "Negritude ou Africanité?" galley proofs Guichard-Meili Guillerme, J. Gurian, S., "La récente publication de l'édition..." Håkanson, Björn Halperin, Ernest, "Statement ... at the Hearings before the Subcommittee on American Republics Affairs of the Committee on Foreign Relations, U.S. Senate..." Halperin, "Molotov et Pekin" Halperin, "La Verite Sur Cuba" Havel, Valclav (Box 649, Folder 5)
    - Manuscripts, Harasymowicz-Hatar, 1955-1962, Harasymowicz, Jerzy Harkat, Mostefa Hartlaub, Felix Hatar, V. G. J. (Box 649, Folder 6)
    - Manuscripts, Hartley-Himy, undated, Hartley, Anthony Hayward, Max Henein Henry Heraud Herbert, Zbigniew Hersch, Jean, "Culture et Liberté" Hersch, "La Tradition selon Karl Jaspers..." Hersch, "La science et l’industrialisation comme aventures spirituelles" Hersch, "Hommage à Karl Jaspers" Hertz, Paul Himy (Box 649, Folder 7)
    - Manuscripts, Hinden-Horne, 1953-1968, Hinden, Rita Hirschman, Albert Hoffman, Stanley, "The French Pschodrama" Hoffman, "La Collaboration en France pendant la Seconde Guerre Mondiale" Hofman, Werner Holappa Hook, Sidney, "Science et Materialisme Dialectique" Hook, "Un Chapitre fatidique de Notre Histoire" Horne (Box 650, Folder 1)
    - Manuscripts, Hottinger-Huxley, undated, Hottinger, Arnold, "Comme l'enfer, l'agitation c'est les autres" Hottinger, "Socialisme Egyptien" Huisinga, J. H. Huxley, Aldous, "Variations sur un theme musical" Huxley, "Des poissens en conserve" (Box 650, Folder 2)
    - Manuscripts, Ierunca-Ionesco, 1949-1965, Ierunca, "Lucian Blaga" Ierunca, "Me trouver aujoued `hui aux..." Ignotius, Paul, "Chronique" Ignotius, "Anniversaire" Ignotius, "Dieux, Sexe et Immortalité" Ionesco, "Victimes du Devoir" Ionesco, "Special Issue Preuves on Ionesco" (Box 650, Folder 3)
    - Manuscripts, Ionesco-Jacot, 1959-1965, Ionesco, "Special Issue Preuves on Ionesco" Ionesco, "Special Issue Preuves on Ionesco" Illakowiczowna, Kazmiera Illyes, Gyula Iwaniuk, Waclaw Iwaszkiewicz, Jaroslaw Jacot, Claude (Box 650, Folder 4)
    - Manuscripts, Jahn-de Jouvenal, 1959-1966, Jahn, Jangeinz Jankowski, Jerzy Jasienski, Bruno Jaspers, Karl, "Preface" Jaspers, "Dangers et chances de la Liberté" Jastrun, Mieczyslaw Jelenski, K. A., "En Octobre 1956, la Pologne..." Jelenski, K. A., "Les poètes polonais ont été..." Jelenski, K. A., "Traduire la poesie..." Jelenski, K. A., "Anthologie de la poesie Polonaise" Jelenski, K. A., "Structures de Gombrowicz" Jelenski, K. A., "Un ‘Monde Secondaire'" Jelenski, K. A., "Les hippies et leurs prophètes" Jelenski, K. A., "Après la Rencontre de Zurich" Jelenski, K. A., "Terre de violence et de remords" Jelenski, K. A., "Leonor Fini et le fantastique contemporain" Jelenski, K. A., "L'engagement de Neizcestony" Jelenski, K. A., "Holeusaï" de Jouvenal, Bertrand, "The Political Economy of Gratuity" (Box 650, Folder 5)
    - Manuscripts, de Jouvenal-Jungk, 1957-1961, de Jouvenal, "Introduction au Probleme de l'Arcadie ‘Sur une page d'Engels'" de Jouvenal, "De l'Economie Politique a l'Ecologie Politique" Juliet Jünger, Ernt Jungk, Robert, "Betriebsblind" Jungk, "La creation et la volonte de l'homme" Jungk, "Die Weltausstellung als moralische Anstalt" (Box 650, Folder 6)
    - Manuscripts, Kaki-Kennedy, 1958-1967, Kaki Kapoor Kardorff Karpinsli Karpowicz, Tymoteusz Kaschnitz Kasprowicz Kattan, Naim Kattan, galley proofs Kende Kende, galley proofs Kennedy (Box 650, Folder 7)
    - Manuscripts, Kennan-Kochanowski, 1966, Kennan, George, "Strategie de la Liberté" Kennan, "La politique mondiale dans la détente" Kennan, "Wilson et les buts de la guerre" Kennan, "Délibérations des Alliés à Paris" Kennan, "Le Monde Non-Europeen" Kennan, "Entretien avec George Kennan" Khair-Eddine Kiesinger Kniaznin Kochanowski (Box 651, Folder 1)
    - Manuscripts, Kochowski-Kristol, 1961-1967, Kochowski Kolozie Konopnicka Konta Kott Krämer-Badoni Krasicki Krasinski Kraus Kriegel Kristol, Irving, "Einstein, The Passion of Pure Reason" Kristol, "Ordeal by Mendacity" Kristol, "Dieu et la Politique aux Etats-Unis" Kristol, "General Electric, Télévision, John F. Kennedy et U.S.A." (Box 651, Folder 2)
    - Manuscripts, Kübler-Kwiatkowski, 1968, Kübler, Arnold, "Das Gastspiel" Kübler, "Tycho-Brahe-Tag" Kuby Kuby, galley proofs Kurek Kwiatkowski (Box 651, Folder 3)
    - Manuscripts, Labin-Laqueur, 1956-1966, Labin, Suzanne, "Il n'y avait aucune base socialiste en Hongrie" Labin, "Reaction des intellectuels communistes a la destalinisation" Labin, "Conservatisme et Progressisme dans la société moderne" Laloy, Jean, "Histoire de la querre froide" Laloy, Jean, "Vers une organization des rapports internationaux" Laloy, "Coexistence, Convergence, Reconciliation" Laloy, "Soloviev et son influence" Lambert-Rucki Landolfi Laporte Lapouge Laqueur, Walter, "Peaceful Coexistence and the Ideological Struggle" Laqueur, "Communisme et Nationalisme en Afrique Tropicale" Laqueur, "La Perse entre la réforme et la révolution" Laqueur, "A Note on Soviet Science Fiction" (Box 651, Folder 4)
    - Manuscripts, Laqueur-Lasky, 1968, Laqueur, "De Breslau à Wroclaw" Laqueur, "Quand M. Hammerskjoeld..." Laqueur, "The Soviet Writers Congress" Larquié, Claude, "La Decouverte de l'Homme" Larquié, "Luttes des classes et les societes paysannes" Larquié, Claude, "Luttes des classes et les societes paysannes", galley proofs Larquié, "L'Histoire em mouvement" Lasky, Melvin, "German Youth Today" Lasky, "Revolution Diary" (Box 651, Folder 5)
    - Manuscripts, Lasky-Leclerq, 1958-1968, Lasky, "Der General und die Landkarte" Lasky, "Das Thema das ich zu behandeln..." Lasky, "Indian Notebook" Laurens Lec, Stanislaws, "Qui n'est Pas sujet..." Lec, Stanislaws, "Reflexions mal lechees" Lec, "Pensées Decoiffées" Lecaye Lechon, Jan Leclerq (Box 651, Folder 6)
    - Manuscripts, LeGoff-Levy, 1965, LeGoff Lejard Lemos Lenartowicz Lendvai Lenin Lennon Lesmian Levine, Norman, "Ringa Ringa Rosie" Levine, "The Lesson" Levine, "The Cocks Are Crowing" Levine, "A Sabbath Walk" Levy, Yves, "Les Cinq Saisons" Levy, "Le 27 Octobre 1937, Elie Faure..." (Box 652, Folder 1)
    - Manuscripts, Levy-Lochak, 1959-1964, Levy, "La Critique de Chaplin et le Realisme Socialiste" Levy, "Nous, les Parents..." Levy, "Le Tremplin" Liebert Listopad Lipset, Seymour, "L'Ascension de Goldwater et l'avenir des Republican" Lipset, "’Backlashes' and Republican Prospects" Lobodowski Lochak, Danièle, "Defense et Illustration du Mouvement Etudiant" Lochak, "En Attendant le Paix..." (Box 652, Folder 2)
    - Manuscripts, Lowenthal, undated, Lowenthal, Richard, "Jenseits das Stalinismus?" Lowenthal, "Konservatives Jugoslawien" Lowenthal, "Revolution Over Eastern Europe" Lowenthal, "Sous le Regne de Krouchtchev" Lowenthal, "Djilas and the Yugoslav Dilemma" (Box 652, Folder 3)
    - Manuscripts, Lowenthal-Lüthy, 1965, Lowenthal, "L'aventure de Tito" Lukacs, Georg Lüthy, Herbert, "Réponse de Herbert Lüthy" Lüthy, "Colonisation, Colonialisme, Decolonisation" Lüthy, "Wo zu Geschichte?" Lüthy, "Les huguenots apres la Revocation" Lüthy, "Les protestants françaises ont-ils fait la Revolution?" Lüthy, "Les Suisse à contre-courant" Lüthy, "L'Europe rest a decoloniser" (Box 652, Folder 4)
    - Manuscripts, McCarthy-Marías, 1954-1968, McCarthy, Mary McGrady, Patrick McKay, Vernon de Madariaga, Salvador, "El Congresso Europeo de Munich" de Madariaga, "Le suerte, que tan sabia es, aunque..." Magrini Magris Mahfouz, Najib, "Contre inconnu" Malczewski, Antoni Mallet, Jacques Marías, Julián, "Notre image de la Ville" Marías, "Note pour Pierre Emmanuel" (Box 652, Folder 5)
    - Manuscripts, Marcel-Masters, 1969, Marcel, Gabriel Marnat, Marcel, "Barbieres Diverses" Marnat, "Artistes ou Techniciens?" Marnat, "Art en Poche" Marnat, "Exotismes" Marnat, "Architecture" Marnat, "Architecture" galley proofs Marnat, "De Pharaon à Maine-Montparnasse" Marnat, "Du regard: Histoire et Utilisation" Martin, René Martin-Chauffier Martins, Wilson Masters, Roger (Box 652, Folder 6)
    - Manuscripts, Mates-Meszoly, 1962, Mates, Leo Mayne, Richard Meier, Victor, "L'Europe de l'Est" Meier, "L'Europe de l'Est" galley proofs Méray, Tibor, "La Vie Eternelle" Méray, "Different from others" Meszoly (Box 653, Folder 1)
    - Manuscripts, Mettre-Mindzenti, undated, Mettre, Claude Miaskowski, Kasper Micinski, Tadeuz Mickiewski, Adam Miedzyrzecki, Artur Milosz, Czeslaw Mindzenti, Laszlo (Box 653, Folder 2)
    - Manuscripts, Mlodozeniec-Musulin, 1960-1963, Mlodozeniec, Stanislaw Molnar, Thomas, "Chapter Nine" Molnar, Miklos Molnar, galley proofs Moltchanov, Nicolas Mormino, Guiseppe Morrison, Stephen Morsztyn, Andrzej Mosquera, Marta Musulin, Janko (Box 653, Folder 3)
    - Manuscripts, Nabakov-Naruszewicz, 1961, Nabakov, Nicholas Naborowski, Daniel Namora, Fernando, "Temoignage, d'un Ecrivain Portugais" Namora, "Ville de Solitude" Nantet, Jacques Naruszewicz, Adam (Box 653, Folder 4)
    - Manuscript, Nesvadba, Josef, "La Decouverte du Dr. Doug," undated (Box 653, Folder 5)
    - Manuscripts, Newman-Ozouf, 1959-1968, Newman, Barnett Newman, galley proofs Nora, Pierre Norwid, Cyprian Nussbaum, Henrich, "Ein Gewissen der Nation" Nussbaum, "Aufbruch nach innen" Nysenholc Ocampo, V. Onégine, Eugéne Oppenheimer Ort, Alexander Ozouf, Jacques (Box 653, Folder 6)
    - Manuscripts, Pacheco-Paz, 1966-1968, Pacheco Paeschke, Hans Pampaloni, Geno Pankowski, Marian Papaioannou, Kostas, "Mythe et Réalité de l'mpérialisme" Papaioannou, "Modernite et Histoire" Paseyro, Ricardo Patri, Aimée, "Ragon chez les Américains" Patri, "Les malheurs de Sophie" Paube, Monique Pawlikowska-Janorzewska, Maria Payot, Roger Paz, Octavia Paz, galley proofs (Box 654, Folder 1)
    - Manuscripts, Peroutka, Ferdinand, "Democratic Manifesto," undated (Box 654, Folder 2)
    - Manuscripts, Peiper-Pliya, 1958-1964, Peiper, Tadeuz Pépin, Jean Pereire, Emmanuel Philip, André Picaper, Jean-Paul Pichard, Joseph Picon, Gaëtan Picon-Salas, Mariano Pietrkiewicz, Jerzy Pillement, Georges, "Pour un Style Moderne" Pillement, "Le Probleme des Halles" Pillement, "Ribeiro Couto" Pineau Pliya, Jean, "L'Arbre Fetiche" Pliya, "Le Gardien de nuit" (Box 654, Folder 3)
    - Manuscripts, Pliya-Preda, undated, Pliya, "Le Chimpanze Amoureaux" Pliya, "La Voiture Rouge" Pliya, "Le Rendez-vous" Potocki, Waclaw Pouchine, A. Preda, Marin, "La Colliere" (Box 654, Folder 4)
    - Manuscripts, Preda-Rodoc, 1957-1968, Preda, "La Rencontre" Preda, "La Colère" Preda, "Chaleur Accablante" Przybos, Julian Pulley, William Rabaut, Jean Rais, Emmanuel Raymond, Marcel Reblitz, Irma Rej, Mikolaj Revel, Jean-François Rewald, Alice, "Les Musees Americains" Rewald, "Eastman-Kodak et le Black Power" Rodoc, M. (Box 654, Folder 5)
    - Manuscripts, Rolicz-Leider-Rudnicki, 1966, Rolicz-Leider, Waclaw Rostworowiski, Jan Roudat, Jean de Rougement, Denis Roudy, Pierre de Roux, Dominique Rozanov Rozewicz, Tadeuz Rudnicki, Henri (Box 654, Folder 6)
    - Manuscripts, Saaverda-Schlesinger, 1959-1963, Saaverda, Carlos St. Jorre, John Sardui Sarkis, Khalil Ramez Sartre, Jean-Paul Savarius, Vincent Scarpi, N. O. Schlesinger, A. M., Jr., "The Shape of National Politics to Come" (Box 655, Folder 1)
    - Manuscripts, Schlesinger-Sefrioui, 1958-1966, Schlesinger, "Origins of the Cold War" Schneider, Pierre, "Preface" Schneider, Pierre, "La Decouverte du Present" Schneider, "Prié par l'Association internationale.. ." Schneider, "The Little Four" Schnurre Schoen Sefrioui, Ahmed (Box 655, Folder 2)
    - Manuscripts, Segre-Souchère, 1941-1960, Segre Seidensticker, Edward Sep-Szarzynski Serge, Victor Sidjanski, Dusan Sieburg, Friedrich Silone, Ignazio Da Silva, José-Gentil Simic, A. B. Slowacki, Juliusz Slonimski, Antoni Slucki, Arnold Smolik, Jan Sommerville, John Sosnora, Victor Souchère, Elena, "Le Regime Franquiste est-il incapable de se.. ." (Box 655, Folder 3)
    - Manuscripts, Souchère-Suhr, 1960-1968, Souchère, "La grande colere des etudiants d'Amerique Latine" Spark, Muriel, "La Transfiguration de l'Ordinaire" Sperber, Manes Spielman, Barbara Spine, Henriette Staff, Leopold Starobinski, Jean Steel, Ronald Stern, Anatol Stern, Laurent Subramanyam, Ka Naa Suda, Zdenek Suheil, Farida, "Histoire a Deux Voix" Suheil, "Les Septs Negresses" Suheil, "Dalila" Suhr, Albert (Box 655, Folder 4)
    - Manuscripts, Sukharov-Tauber, undated, Sukharov, N. N. Suliny, F. Sulkowski, Tadeuz Svabe, A. Syzmborska, Wieslawa Szymonowicz, Szymon Syrokomla, Wladyslaw Szabo, Laszlo Taieb, Hajd Tardes, Tibor Tas, S. Tauber, Christian (Box 655, Folder 5)
    - Manuscripts, Tavernier-Torielli, 1961-1968, Tavernier, Rene Terzakis, Anghélos, "Le Choeur Tragique" Tetmajer, Kazimierz Texier, Jean Thiery, André, "La Grande-Bretagne et l'innaccessible Marche Commun" Thiery, "L'Europe, Evenement Historique?" Thiery, "L'Europe des Chancelleries" Thomas, Hans Thomas, Henri Tigrid, Pavel Torielli, Carlo (Box 655, Folder 6)
    - Manuscripts, Touchard-Tuwim, 1964, Touchard, Pierre Tourret, F. Trembecki, Stanislaw Tucci, Niccolo Tussman, Lorrie Tütsch, Hans Tuwim, Julian (Box 656, Folder 1)
    - Manuscripts, Uri-Vanetti, 1965, Uri, Pierre Vago, Pierre Vaillant, Annette, "Avant l'U.R.S.S." Vaillant, "Madame Sarah Bernhardt" Vaillant, Annette, "Ne Dis Pas Qu'Il Est Amarant" Vaillant, "Protee" Vaillant, "Merci, Monsieur Vuillard" Vanderlinden, E. Vanetti, Dolores, "Le noel de la princesse" Vanetti, "Une fleur et un numero" (Box 656, Folder 2)
    - Manuscripts, Vassilikos-La Ville, 1968, Vassilikos, Vassilis Vermont, Rene La Ville et l'Imaginaire: Manuscripts for special issue (Box 656, Folder 3)
    - Manuscripts, Villon-Weigend-Abendroth, 1948-1962, Villon, Jacques Vineuil, Jean Viraghati, Laszlo Vittorini, Elio Vladine, K. Volkoff, Alexis Wandurski, Witold Wat, Aleksander Wazyk, Adam Weigend-Abendroth, Von Friedrich (Box 656, Folder 4)
    - Manuscripts, Wierzynski-Zimorowicz, 1964, Wierzynski, Kazimierz Winczakiewicz, Jan Witkiewicz, S. I. Wirpsza Wittlin, Jozef Witwicki, Stefan Wlodzimierz, Brus Wood Krutch, Joseph Worms, Jeannine Woroszylski, Wiktor Wucher, Albert Wyspianski, Stanislaw Yourcenar, Margeurite Zellwenger, E. Zemzs, Abraham, "D'un code pictural á L'autre" Zimorowicz, Szymon (Box 656, Folder 5)
    - Manuscript Fragments, Identified, undated, Bloch-Michel Bondy Brzezinski, Z. Caillois Friedrich, Hugo Gombrich Torielli (Box 656, Folder 6)
    - Manuscript fragments, 19651-1966 (Box 657, Folder 1)
    - Manuscript fragments, 1958-1960 (Box 657, Folder 2)
    - Manuscript fragments, 1961-1964 (Box 657, Folder 3)
    - Manuscript fragments, Unidentified (Box 657, Folder 4)
    - Manuscript fragments, Unidentified (Box 657, Folder 5)
  - Subseries 21: Book Fairs and Exhibitions
    - Brussels, 1958 (Box 657, Folder 6)
    - Frankfurt, 1960-1968 (Box 658, Folder 1)
    - Paris, 1960-1969 (Box 658, Folder 2)
  - Subseries 22: Photographs
    - Bookstores Displays, undated (Box 658, Folder 3)
    - Prevues Anniversary Parties and Conferences, Photographs, 1952-1954 (Box 658, Folder 4)
    - Prevues Anniversary Parties and Conferences, Photographs, 1954-1955 (Box 658, Folder 5)
- Series VIII: Edward Shils Papers, 1958-1975
  This series contains correspondence to and from Edward Shils. This series is divided into four small subseries, which relate to the series to which the correspondence relates. Within each subseries, correspondence is arranged alphabetically by topic or by person.
  - Subseries 1: Correspondence from Series I
    - Correspondence, P, 1958 (Box 659, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, A-V, 1959 (Box 659, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, F-V, 1960 (Box 659, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, C, 1967 (Box 659, Folder 4)
  - Subseries 2: Correspondence from Series II
    - Administrative, Executive Committee, 1964 (Box 659, Folder 5)
    - Administrative, General Assembly, 1967 (Box 659, Folder 6)
    - Administrative, General Assembly, 1969 (Box 659, Folder 7)
    - Africa, African Bureau, 1960 (Box 659, Folder 8)
    - Africa, Correspondence, 1965 (Box 659, Folder 9)
    - Arab Democracy, 1960 (Box 659, Folder 10)
    - Arab Writers, 1960 (Box 659, Folder 11)
    - Asia, 1964 (Box 659, Folder 12)
    - Australian Association for Cultural Freedom, 1965-1969 (Box 659, Folder 13)
    - Bieber, Marion, 1962-1963 (Box 659, Folder 14)
    - Board of Directors, 1967 (Box 659, Folder 15)
    - Board of Directors, minutes and reports, 1970-1973 (Box 659, Folder 16)
    - CCF, Planning Committee, 1958 (Box 659, Folder 17)
    - Central Intelligence Agency, 1966 (Box 659, Folder 18)
    - Committee on Science and Freedom, 1958 (Box 659, Folder 19)
    - Committee on Science and Freedom, Minerva, 1962 (Box 659, Folder 20)
    - Committee on Social Thought, 1973 (Box 659, Folder 21)
    - Duerdon, Dennis, 1962 (Box 659, Folder 22)
    - Duffy, Joseph, 1973 (Box 659, Folder 23)
    - Emmanuel, Pierre, 1973-1975 (Box 659, Folder 24)
    - Encounter, 1967 (Box 659, Folder 25)
    - Ford Foundation, 1961 (Box 659, Folder 26)
    - Geertz, Clifford, 1961 (Box 659, Folder 27)
    - Goldstein, David, 1971 (Box 659, Folder 28)
    - Goldstein-Goodwin, 1968-969 (Box 659, Folder 29)
    - Hudson, Geoffrey, 1960 (Box 659, Folder 30)
    - Hungary, Philharmonica, 1960 (Box 659, Folder 31)
    - Hunt, John, 1960 (Box 659, Folder 32)
    - IACF, 1967-1968 (Box 659, Folder 33)
    - India, 1958 (Box 659, Folder 34)
    - India, Bombay, 1965-1976 (Box 659, Folder 35)
    - India, Quest, 1972 (Box 659, Folder 36)
    - India, Quest and New Quest, 1975-1976 (Box 659, Folder 37)
    - India, Quest and New Quest, 1977-1978 (Box 659, Folder 38)
    - Iribarne, Don Manuel Fraga, 1965 (Box 659, Folder 39)
    - Japan, Jazz Seminar, 1960 (Box 659, Folder 40)
    - Jelenski, K.A., 1964 (Box 659, Folder 41)
    - Jelenski, K.A., 1968-1973 (Box 659, Folder 42)
    - Josselson, Michael, 1958-1966 (Box 659, Folder 43)
    - Josselson, Michael, 1960-1972 (Box 660, Folder 1)
    - de Jouvenel, Bertrand, 1961 (Box 660, Folder 2)
    - Laqueur, Walter, 1959 (Box 660, Folder 3)
    - Latin America, 1964 (Box 660, Folder 4)
    - Levinson, Joseph, 1960 (Box 660, Folder 5)
    - Lewis, Arthur, 1961 (Box 660, Folder 6)
    - Michael, Franz, 1960 (Box 660, Folder 7)
    - Minerva, 1962-1965 (Box 660, Folder 8)
    - Minerva, 1969-1974 (Box 660, Folder 9)
    - Minerva, 1975-1977 (Box 660, Folder 10)
    - Minerva, 1978 (Box 660, Folder 11)
    - Minerva, Samuel Boggio, 1964 (Box 660, Folder 12)
    - Pasternak, undated (Box 660, Folder 13)
    - Passin, Herbert, 1956 (Box 660, Folder 14)
    - Saran-Schwartz, 1960-1962 (Box 660, Folder 15)
    - Scientific Policy, 1960 (Box 660, Folder 16)
    - Shils, Edward, 1953-1959 (Box 660, Folder 17)
    - Shils, Edward, 1960-1961 (Box 660, Folder 18)
    - Shils, Edward, 1962-1965 (Box 660, Folder 19)
    - Shils, Edward, 1967-1968 (Box 660, Folder 20)
    - Shils, Edward, 1969-1975 (Box 660, Folder 21)
    - Shils, Edward, 1972 (Box 660, Folder 22)
    - Spanish Universities, 1965 (Box 661, Folder 1)
    - Stone, Shepherd, 1968-1974 (Box 661, Folder 2)
    - Survey, 1974 (Box 661, Folder 3)
    - Transition, 1968 (Box 661, Folder 4)
    - Transition, 1974 (Box 661, Folder 5)
    - Wacker, Jeanne, 1960 (Box 661, Folder 6)
    - Yugoslav Seminar, 1959-1960 (Box 661, Folder 7)
  - Subseries 3: Correspondence from Series III
    - Khartoum Seminar, 1962 (Box 661, Folder 8)
    - New Dehli Seminar, 1960 (Box 661, Folder 9)
    - Rhodes Seminar, 1959 (Box 661, Folder 10)
    - Seminars, 1960 (Box 661, Folder 11)
  - Subseries 4: General Correspondence
    - Goldstein, David, 1973-1974 (Box 661, Folder 12)
    - Financial, Edward Shils, 1957-1963 (Box 661, Folder 13)
    - Shah, A.B., 1966-1971 (Box 661, Folder 14)
    - Shils, Edward, 1960-1970 (Box 661, Folder 15)
    - Shils, Edward, 1967-1974 (Box 661, Folder 16)
    - Shils, Edward, 1969-1970 (Box 661, Folder 17)
    - Shils, Edward, 1967-1968 (Box 661, Folder 18)
    - Shils, Edward, 1969-1975 (Box 661, Folder 19)